https://www.rossitertrust.com/privacy-notice/

0
was successfully added to your cart.
Basket
Privacy Policy
The Stuart Rossiter Trust Privacy Policy
1.  Privacy Commitment
The Stuart Rossiter Trust (the Trust) is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy has been created using Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) guidance.
2.  Collecting and handling data
The Trust will hold and process the personal information which you provide via the Trust’s website(s) or by submitting emails or online forms for organisational and promotional purposes in the following ways:
a.  Postal, E mail and Telephone Privacy Policy
If you supply the Trust with your telephone number, you may receive telephone contact from the Trust with information. You may also receive telephone contact from the Trust with information regarding new services, online surveys, or upcoming events. If you supply the Trust with your postal address you may receive periodic mailings from the Trust with information on new services or forthcoming events. Your email address may be used by the Trust to notify you about updates to the site and/or contact you for marketing and informational purposes.
b.  Newsletter
When the Trust uses a third party provider, (e.g. MailChimp, or other tools) to deliver its online information and newsletter services these tools gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies to help monitor and improve the e-service.
c.  Security and performance
When the Trust uses a third party service to help maintain the security and performance of its websites it processes the IP addresses of visitors to the Trust website(s).
d. Use of Cookies
In addition to the information you submit to the Trust via the websites, the Trust may collect information about visits to the websites. The Trust collects information on the page browser access. This is used within the Trust to improve the design and layout of its websites. The Trust gathers information on the relative popularity of each page, the average number of pages accessed by visitors, the number of emails sent or files downloaded, and the average time spent on the site. None of this information is linked back to you as an individual. The website(s) may use the following cookies on each page:
i. Session cookies – to enhance your browsing quality by allowing the Trust to know what pages you visit on this website and others.
ii. Google Analytics – the Trust may use this information to compile reports on website usage, visitor sources and analyse browser versions.
3.  Data disclosure to third parties
The Trust does not sell personal information nor will it pass on online personal information to any organisation or individual outside of its control.
4.  Active consent
Please note that by ticking a consent button or any other method requesting active consent included in the website(s) or newsletter or other instance whilst sending your personal information to the Trust you are explicitly consenting to the processing and transfer of such information.
5.  External links
The Trust may provide hyperlinks from the websites to websites of third parties. Please note that this privacy statement applies only to the contents of the Trust website(s) and not to those websites to which the Trust may provide a link.
6.  Changes to this privacy policy
The Trust keeps its privacy notice under regular review. This privacy notice was last updated on 31st October 2018.
7.  Contact us
If you write to us, the Trust will provide details of any personal information which you have provided us with (this may be at a small charge). The Trust may require proof of identity from you prior to disclosing such information, in order to safeguard the security of your information.  Please contact us by email to srtcorr@gmail.com or by post to: The Stuart Rossiter Trust c/o 56 James Street, Selsey, Chichester PO20 0JG
About usAbout us
About Stuart Rossiter
Charity Commission
Objectives
Trustees
Privacy Notice
Contact us
Book ShopBook Shop
Corresponding Trustee: Andy Gould, 56 James Street, Selsey, Chichester, PO20 0JG, U.K. Email: srtcorr@gmail.com
© 2020 Stuart Rossiter Trust.
